informationliberation.com 2019-12-24

# InformationLiberation | The news you're not supposed to know...

**InformationLiberation's Privacy Policy** At InformationLiberation.com ("Information Liberation", "we," or "us"), we are committed to ensuring the privacy of our users. This Privacy Policy ("Policy") describes how personal information is collected from users of the InformationLiberation's Web site located at www.informationliberation.com ("Site"), and how that information is used and disclosed. By using our Site, you consent to the terms of this Policy.

 **What is Personal Information?**

Personal information is information that specifically identifies an individual, such as a user's name, address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card or other account number, and information about that individual's activities when directly linked to that person such as information about his or her purchases or use of services. Personal information also includes demographic information such as date of birth, gender, geographic area and preferences when such information is linked to other personal information that identifies you.

Personal information does not include "aggregate" information. Aggregate information is data we collect about a group or category of products, services or users from which individual user identities have been removed. In other words, information about how you use a service may be collected and combined with information about how others use the same service, but no personal information will be included in the resulting data. Aggregate data helps us understand trends and user needs so that we can better consider new products and services, and tailor existing products and services to user desires.

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our news digest or fill out a form. 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address.

This website uses Google Analytics to monitor and track our traffic stats. Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google. Google utilizes the data collected to track and examine the use of www.informationliberation.com, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services. Google may use the data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network. Read about their service here: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/> Read about their range of options to opt out of their tracking services here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/>

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.

Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy: [http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

 **What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

\- To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

\- To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

\- To send periodic emails

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

 **Do we use cookies?**

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

 **Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

 **Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website, including Amazon Affiliate links. We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit My Settings' page.

 **Children**

We do not intend, and the Site is not designed, to collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old, you should not register with or otherwise provide personal information to our Site.

 **Terms and Conditions**

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at [http://www.informationliberation.com/?disclaimer](https://www.informationliberation.com/?disclaimer)

 **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on _Tuesday, August 20th, 2019._

If you have any questions about this Policy, or the practices of or your dealings with the Site, please email us at: webmaster(at)informationliberation.com
